<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MOKEYISH&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://yish.vip/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MOKEYISH&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 21:46:59 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://yish.vip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example</title>
      <link>http://yish.vip/post/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 21:46:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yish.vip/post/example/</guid>
      <description>不就是几分钟的事情吗？我可以多写几行的。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mongoose OS on ESPer</title>
      <link>http://yish.vip/post/mos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 18:59:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yish.vip/post/mos/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve got my hands on the craved-for IoT ESP32, thanks to DFRobot, and have been tinkering with it ever since. I&amp;rsquo;m really amazed by it since it packs both Bluetooth and WiFi in a small yet powerful unit. Since I received the MCU rather than the module, so, to use it, I made myself a breakout board named ESPer(because, why not? 😄). Feel free to check out its Instructable over here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing &#34;django-netjsonconfig&#34;</title>
      <link>http://yish.vip/post/netjsonconfig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 14:28:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yish.vip/post/netjsonconfig/</guid>
      <description>A task came up in Google Code-in which asked me to install the django-netjsonconfig module by OpenWISP. Furthermore, I&amp;rsquo;m also supposed to share the challenges I faced during the set-up process as a sort of feedback. I&amp;rsquo;ll be trying be concise in this post so, without further ado, I&amp;rsquo;m beginning with this post.
Installing &amp;ldquo;django-netjsonconfig&amp;rdquo; The installation instructions for this this module have been well-documented on its GitHub repository. So I began the installation by creating a Python 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Code-in with OpenWISP</title>
      <link>http://yish.vip/post/gci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 10:29:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yish.vip/post/gci/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been participating in Google Code-in which is Google&amp;rsquo;s initiative to introduce young minds to the concept of FOSS, that is Free or Open-Source Softwares. This post is for sharing my experiences with GCI, as the title suggests. So let&amp;rsquo;s just get on it.
It all began while I was returning from an outing on 5 December, 2017 and was searching the internet for Google Science Fair to check if I could participate in it or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yish.vip/404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yish.vip/404/</guid>
      <description> Error 404: Page Not Found It seems that the page that you&amp;rsquo;re trying to access doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist. 😟 If you&amp;rsquo;re sure that it exists, chances are it might have been moved to a new link! You may search for it on the home page. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yish.vip/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yish.vip/about/</guid>
      <description>So, Who Am I? 
I’m just another person who likes writing, programming and making stuff. Even setting the title as Who Am I for this article is reminding me of whoami in Linux. I feel the inner urge to contribute something to the Internet because I love writing and I believe posting something online enables users all around the globe to see your work and suggest improvements.
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve also started taking interest in web designing and hosting the fruitful results of which these site and blogs are!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>